呼叫
Call
雪莉
Shirley
以前从未用奶油制成过的鲜奶油
Whipped cream never made with cream before
我只有奶油
I've only had whipped cream
今天就像在Keswick
It's going to be like in Keswick today
我进来之前就这么说了
I said this before I came in
少数会变得贫穷吗
Is it going to be poor in a few
奶油单位
Units of cream
不好了
Oh no
哦，这是在碗里
Oh this is in a bowl
我想你把这个放在粉状的东西里
I think you put this in here powdered stuff
婴儿小苏打
Baby baking soda
我确定有一个适当的数量，我不知道那是什么
I'm sure there's an appropriate amount I don't know what that is
我不是维多利亚时代的女士，戴头盔
I'm not a lady from the Victorian use a helmet
好的，这正在发生
Ok this is happening
冒泡
Bubbling
Twerking
阿南达·沙克
Ananda Shake
直到我们鲜奶油
Until we have whipped cream
这需要多长时间
How long will it take
冰箱
Freezer
提示
Suggesting
我要用奶油和自制奶油加奶油制作，我需要一个碗
I'm going to make with cream and homemade whipped cream with cream I need a bowl
首先从冰箱的孔开始，因为东西的拐角处
Starting with a bore straight from the freezer because the corner of things are
重奶油
Heavy cream
您得到巴氏杀菌牛奶将变得更加轻松快捷
You get pasteurized milk it will be easier and faster
对于重奶油
For the heavy cream in
我给你做了一点糖粉
I made you a little powdered sugar
这比我的颗粒更容易破碎，我更喜欢颗粒，因为
That is going to break up a little easier than my granulated I prefer granulated because
里面有玉米淀粉，味道很好
Has cornstarch in it and it tastes so good
我通常会以这种方式对一个人这样做，因为它基本上只是来回
I would normally do it this way for a person that ever it's basically just a back and forth as a
如果我每天都这样做，我会流汗，我再也不需要做任何其他事情了
I'm sweating if I do this everyday I would never have to do any sort of our next
这是新金
This is new gold
您是爱情之星，所以您无法一饱眼福
You are a star on love so there doesn't get all over you
我们会越来越像这样吗
Will it start to look like this we getting close
我能看到打浆机的涟漪吗，因为
Can I see the ripples from the beaters because
在我的循环蛋白酥皮上50周，您可能会做黄油
50 weeks on my cycle meringue you might make butter
成功
Success
那个声音
That sound
那是我的女王
That's my queen
鲜奶油
Whipped cream
那很棒
That's great
把我的脸放在雪地里
Put my face in the snow
寻找到湖畔
Navigate to Lakeside
我最差的时候要做的是喝一杯凉啤酒
What I'm going to do this at my worst have a nice cold beer
这是一个不错的冷浓奶油
It's a nice cold heavy cream
然后我们要添加一些糖，这是关键
And then we're going to add some sugar and this is key
人们倾向于在奶油中放两种不同类型的糖
Is two different types of sugar people tend to put in whipped cream
我喜欢用这种飞机砂糖好吗
What I like to use this plane granulated sugar ok
糖果糖和一般的神奇宝贝开始了吗，我觉得这让我的工作发挥了作用
Is confectioners sugar and generally Pokémon starting this and I feel like it makes my work play mode on
我刚好吃了一些糖就可以使奶油变甜
Something I just enough sugar to get a sweet up the cream
我之所以能赚到钱，是因为如果以后再有它，我的工作将会很棒
And the reason that I earned it now it's because if we had it later my work is going to be great
导航到我们的废物，并在本周的开始鞭打
Navigate to our waste and start whipping in this week's
当我们为您希望时，会有风险，这样您就可以看到我凝视的时刻正在冒泡，并希望
And when we wish for you there a risk so you can see when I was staring was making a bubble go right now and wish
握住球会产生大量气泡，给自己带来一些稳定性
It's making a ton of bubbles give yourself a little stability by holding onto the ball
现在生病了，我们想把它鞭打到柔软的峰顶，我不想太过分了
Getting sick now we want to whip this to soft Peaks right I don't want to go too far with it
它会前进吗
Is it going to forward
最终替代的甜黄油又好又蓬松
Eventually alternative sweet butter nice and fluffy
是形式可以在我的愿望之上真正柔软如天鹅绒般柔软
Is forms can a really soft velvety piece on the top of my wish
好了，我完成了
Ok I'm done